Guide to the Language Resource Center collection, circa 1963-1983.
Language Resource Center collection,
- Reel-to-reel tape recordings
  - Cornell material
    - Nasilp Indonesian, Undated; TR-12815 (Box 51)
      LRC #: INS 8.2
    - Nasilp Indonesian, Undated; TR-12816 (Box 51)
      LRC #: INS 8.3
    - Nasilp Indonesian, Undated; TR-12817 (Box 51)
      LRC #: INS 8.4
    - Nasilp Indonesian, Undated; TR-12818 (Box 51)
      LRC #: INS 8.5
    - Nasilp Indonesian, Undated; TR-12819 (Box 51)
      LRC #: INS 8.6
    - Nasilp Indonesian, Undated; TR-12820 (Box 51)
      LRC #: INS 9.1
    - Nasilp Indonesian, Undated; TR-12821 (Box 51)
      LRC #: INS 9.2
    - Nasilp Indonesian, Undated; TR-12822 (Box 51)
      LRC #: INS 9.3
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12823 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 0
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12824 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 1-2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12825 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 18.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12826 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 19.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12827 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 19.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12828 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 20.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12829 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 20.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12830 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 20.3
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12831 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 21
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12832 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 22.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12833 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 22.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12834 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 23.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12835 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 23.2
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12836 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 3
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12837 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 4.1
    - Spoken and Written Hindi, Undated; TR-12838 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HN 4.2
    - Hindi LLS, Undated; TR-12839 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNL 1
    - Hindi LLS, Undated; TR-12840 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNL 2
    - Hindi LLS, Undated; TR-12841 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNL 3
    - Hindi LLS, Undated; TR-12842 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNL 4
    - Hindi LLS, Undated; TR-12843 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNL 5
    - Hindi LLS, Undated; TR-12844 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNL 6
    - Hindi LLS, Undated; TR-12845 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNL 7
    - Hindi LLS, Undated; TR-12846 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNL 8
    - Spoken Hindi Master, Undated; TR-12847 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNO 1
    - Spoken Hindi Master, Undated; TR-12848 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNO 2
    - Spoken Hindi Master, Undated; TR-12849 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNO 3
    - Spoken Hindi Master, Undated; TR-12850 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNO 4
    - Spoken Hindustani, Undated; TR-12851 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNS 1
    - Spoken Hindustani, Undated; TR-12852 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNS 2
    - Spoken Hindustani, Undated; TR-12853 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNS 3
    - Hindi Test 1, Undated; TR-12854 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNT 1
    - Hindi Test 4, Undated; TR-12855 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNT 4
    - Hindi Test 5, Undated; TR-12856 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNT 5
    - Hindi Test 6, Undated; TR-12857 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNT 6
    - Hindi Comprehension Exercises, Undated; TR-12858 (Box 55)
      LRC #: HNX 1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12859 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12860 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 10.1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12861 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 10.2
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12862 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 11
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12863 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 12.1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12864 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 12.2
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12865 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 13
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12866 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 14
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12867 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 15.1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12868 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 15.2
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12869 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 15.3
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12870 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 15.4
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12871 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 15.5
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12872 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 16.1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12873 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 16.2
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12874 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 16.3
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12875 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 16.4
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12876 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 17
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12877 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 18
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12878 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 19.1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12879 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 19.2
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12880 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 19.3
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12881 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 19.4
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12882 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 2
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12883 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 20.1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12884 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 20.2
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12885 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 21
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12886 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 22
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12887 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 23
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12888 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 24.1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12889 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 24.2
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12890 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 25
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12891 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 26
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12892 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 27
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12893 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 28.1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12894 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 28.2
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12895 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 29.1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12896 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 29.2
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12897 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 29.3
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12898 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 29.4
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12899 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 29.5
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12900 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 3
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12901 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 30.1
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12902 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 30.2
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12903 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 30.3
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12904 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 30.4
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12905 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 4
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12906 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 5
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12907 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 6
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12908 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 7
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12909 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 8
    - Turkish (FSI), Undated; TR-12910 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TK 9
    - Turkish (Babby), Undated; TR-12911 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TKB 3
    - Turkish (Babby), Undated; TR-12912 (Box 56)
      LRC #: TKB 4
    - Turkish Grammar, Undated; TR-12913 (Box 57)
      LRC #: TKG 17
    - Turkish Grammar, Undated; TR-12914 (Box 57)
      LRC #: TKG 18
    - Turkish Grammar, Undated; TR-12915 (Box 57)
      LRC #: TKG 19
    - Turkish Grammar, Undated; TR-12916 (Box 57)
      LRC #: TKG 20
    - Turkish Grammar, Undated; TR-12917 (Box 57)
      LRC #: TKG 21
    - Turkish Grammar, Undated; TR-12918 (Box 57)
      LRC #: TKG 22
    - Zakaj ne po Slovensko, Undated; TR-12919 (Box 57)
      LRC #: SLT 1
    - En Camino Lesson 20, Undated; TR-12920 (Box 57)
      LRC #: SEN 20
    - Various Linguistic Recordings, Undated; TR-12921 (Box 63)
      LRC #: LVR 1
    - Various Linguistic Recordings, Undated; TR-12922 (Box 63)
      LRC #: LVR 2
    - Various Linguistic Recordings, Undated; TR-12923 (Box 63)
      LRC #: LVR 3
    - Various Linguistic Recordings, Undated; TR-12924 (Box 63)
      LRC #: LVR 4
    - Various Linguistic Recordings, Undated; TR-12925 (Box 63)
      LRC #: LVR 5
    - Various Linguistic Recordings, Undated; TR-12926 (Box 63)
      LRC #: LVR 6
    - Bolaang Mongodov, 1968; TR-12927; Wolff, J. U.; Cornell DMLL; Master (Box 63)
      LRC #: LB 1
    - Bolaang Mongodov, 1968; TR-12928; Wolff, J. U.; Cornell DMLL; Master (Box 63)
      LRC #: LB 2
    - “Auction” (English), Undated; TR-12929; Cornell DMLL (Box 63)
      About 1 br. of an auction - field recording
      LRC #: LM 4
    - Phonetics - Ling 101, 1976; TR-12930; Smith, Ian; Cornell DMLL (Box 63)
      This tape illustrates the various sounds represented by the symbols on the 2 charts handed out in LING 101
      LRC #: LM 5
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12931; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 1
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12932; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 10
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12933; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 11
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12934; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 12
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12935; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 13
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12936; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 14
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12937; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 15
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12938; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 16
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12939; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 17
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12940; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 18
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12941; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 19
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12942; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 2
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12943; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 20
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12944; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 21
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12945; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 22
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12946; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 23
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12947; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 24
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12948; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 25
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12949; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 26
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12950; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 27
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12951; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 28
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12952; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 29
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12953; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 3
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12954; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 30
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12955; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 31
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12956; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 32
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12957; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 33
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12958; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 4
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12959; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 5
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12960; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 6
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12961; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 7
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12962; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 8
    - Manual of Articulatory Phonetics, 1963; TR-12963; Smalley; Practical Anthropology (Box 64)
      LRC #: LP 9
    - Taiwanese Amoy - Bodruau Wu Revision, Undated; TR-12964 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TS 5
    - Taiwanese Amoy - Bodruau Wu Revision, Undated; TR-12965 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TS 6
    - 10 Taiwanese Plays / Phonetics, Undated; TR-12966 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TSQ
    - Speak Taiwanese, Undated; TR-12967 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TSQ 6
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12968 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 1
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12969 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 10
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12970 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 11
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12971 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 12
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12972 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 13
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12973 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 2
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12974 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 3
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12975 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 4
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12976 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 5
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12977 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 6
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12978 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 7
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12979 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 8
    - German Exercises, Undated; TR-12980 (Box 43)
      LRC #: GLX 9
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12981 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 1
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12982 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 10
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12983 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 11
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12984 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 12
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12985 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 13
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12986 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 14
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12987 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 15
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12988 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 16
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12989 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 17
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12990 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 18
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12991 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 19
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12992 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 2
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12993 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 20
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12994 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 21
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12995 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 22
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12996 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 3
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12997 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 4
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12998 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 5
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-12999 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 6
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-13000 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 7
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-13001 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 8
    - Portuguese Language Project, Undated; TR-13002 (Box 59)
      LRC #: PTR 9
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13003; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 1
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13004; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 10
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13005; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 11
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13006; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 12
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13007; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 13
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13008; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 14
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13009; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 15
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13010; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 16
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13011; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 17
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13012; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 18
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13013; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 19
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13014; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 2
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13015; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 20
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13016; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 21
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13017; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 22
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13018; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 23
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13019; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 24
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13020; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 25
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13021; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 26
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13022; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 27
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13023; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 28
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13024; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 29
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13025; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 3
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13026; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 30
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13027; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 31
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13028; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 4
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13029; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 5
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13030; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 6
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13031; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 7
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13032; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 8
    - Ancient Greek - A New Approach, 1977; TR-13033; Rook, Carl A. P.; Cornell DMLL (Box 61)
      LRC #: GKC 9
    - Burmese Drills, 1980; TR-13034 (Box 61)
      Duplicated from record EP 89005
      LRC #: BUX 1
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13035; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 10
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13036; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 11
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13037; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 12
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13038; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 13
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13039; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 14
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13040; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 15
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13041; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 16
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13042; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 17
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13043; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 18
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13044; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 19
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13045; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 2
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13046; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 20
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13047 (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 21
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13048; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 3
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13049; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 4
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13050; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 5
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13051; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 7
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13052; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 8
    - Burmese Drills, 1966; TR-13053; Master. Lab copies done. 7.5 IPS. (Box 61)
      LRC #: BUX 9
  - LCTL published
    - Chinese Opera - Mandarin, 1974-12-17; TR-13054; Yuji Hen; Peking Opera; 7.5 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, foiled (Box 2)
      The Red Lantern
      LRC #: MO 1
    - Chinese Opera - Mandarin, 1974-12-17; TR-13055; Yuji Hen; Peking Opera; 7.5 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, foiled (Box 2)
      LRC #: MO 2
    - Chinese Opera - Mandarin, 1974-12-17; TR-13056; Yuji Hen; Peking Opera; 7.5 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, foiled (Box 2)
      LRC #: MO 3
    - Chinese Opera - Mandarin, 1974-12-17; TR-13057; Yuji Hen; Peking Opera; 7.5 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, foiled (Box 2)
      LRC #: MO 4
    - Chinese Opera - Mandarin, 1975-02-21; TR-13058; Yuji Hen; Peking Opera; 7.5 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, foiled (Box 2)
      LRC #: MO 5
    - Chinese Opera - Mandarin, 1975-02-23; TR-13059; Yuji Hen; Peking Opera; 7.5 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, foiled (Box 2)
      LRC #: MO 6
    - Chinese Opera - Mandarin, 1975-02-23; TR-13060; Yuji Hen; Peking Opera; 7.5 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, foiled (Box 2)
      LRC #: MO 7
    - Chinese Opera - Mandarin, 1975-03-13; TR-13061; Yuji Hen; Peking Opera; 7.5 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, foiled (Box 2)
      LRC #: MO 8
    - Chinese Opera - Mandarin, 1983-04-22; TR-13062; Yuji Hen; Peking Opera; 7.5 IPS, half track, mono, one side, dubbing master, foiled (Box 2)
      LRC #: MO 9
    - Intermediate Readings in Modern Chinese, 1977-08-31; TR-13063; Mills; Ni; head tail foil, track a, original (Box 2)
      L13 reading 1
      LRC #: MME 12
    - Intermediate Readings in Modern Chinese, 1977-08-31; TR-13064; Mills; Ni; head tail foil, track a, original (Box 2)
      L14 reading 2
      LRC #: MME 13
    - Intermediate Readings in Modern Chinese, 1977-08-31; TR-13065; Mills; Ni; head tail foil, track a, original (Box 2)
      L 16 reading 3
      LRC #: MME 14
    - Intermediate Readings in Modern Chinese, 1977-08-31; TR-13066; Mills; Ni; head tail foil, track a, original (Box 2)
      L 17 reading 4
      LRC #: MME 15
    - Intermediate Readings in Modern Chinese, 1977-08-31; TR-13067; Mills; Ni; head tail foil, track a, original (Box 2)
      reading 5 and supp reading
      LRC #: MME 16
    - Intermediate Readings in Modern Chinese, 1977-08-31; TR-13068; Mills; Ni; head tail foil, track a, original, 3.75 IPS (Box 2)
      proclaimation on "Cultural Construction on a Chinese Basis; L19 pp142-148
      LRC #: MME 19
    - Intermediate Readings in Modern Chinese, 1977-04-15; TR-13069; Mills; Ni; head tail foil, original,, 3.75 IPS (Box 2)
      L 20 May 4th movement pp149-59
      LRC #: MME 20
    - Intermediate Readings in Modern Chinese, 1977-04-15; TR-13070; Mills; Ni; head tail foil, track a, original,, 3.75 IPS (Box 2)
      L 21 Popular Literature pp160-164
      LRC #: MME 21